freeads.in 2014-04-20

# 

**Privacy Policy**

FreeAds.in respects our client's right to privacy online. We hold detailed client information in confidence.

**Asking for your information**

We will sometimes ask clients for personal information such as you name, address, e-mail address, occupation, hobbies and other details. Providing us your information will simply help us offer products and services that we think you'd like to hear about. When you choose to give personal information to us over the Internet that we or our business partners may request, we will endeavor to inform you how we will use the information. When we ask for personal information for any reason, we will provide a link to this policy statement to make our intentions clear.

**Personal Information Privacy**

FreeAds.in will take all appropriate steps to keep your personal information confidential. Those steps include limiting access to client information databases, communicating this policy statement to all FreeAds.in employees and establishing and enforcing penalties for violating this statement. FreeAds.in will not sell, rent, or give away our clients' personal information to other companies for them to use in selling others' products or services. When we do contract with another company to market or advertise products or services for us, we will insist on binding agreements from those companies protecting our client information. We will vigorously enforce all privacy agreements we have with other companies. We gather personal information from our clients so we can better develop our relationship with those clients. Occasionally, we seek client comments on our products and services. These comments allow us to determine which products and services our clients should be made aware of based on their specific needs. We will communicate with clients via e-mail or other online delivery devices only if the client agrees to receive those communications. Clients, who believe they are receiving our communications in error or no longer desire to receive them, should inform us and we will remove those clients' names from our mailing lists. FreeAds.in will be judicious in the use of e-mail and paper mail to communicate with clients. We will, at all times, put ourselves in the place of the recipients of our mail and treat our clients as we ourselves would like to be treated. FreeAds.in has teamed with others to provide our clients with enhanced Internet services. In providing such services, our business partners also may request personal information from our clients. We prohibit these business partners from selling or giving away our client information and we require them to have a posted Privacy Policy, so that our clients may review it before providing personal information to our business partners. 

**Cookies**

FreeAds.in currently uses a "cookie" on our site. No cookies are placed on the user's computer. A cookie is placed on our server for as long as the session is active. No data from the user's computer is accessed from our site. Our cookies tag each visitor's browser with a random, unique number. The cookie simply assigns a number and does not disclose any personal information about the person using the browser. By noting where these uniquely numbered browsers go on our site, we can study traffic patterns and improve our site. Freeads.in will only logs information related to your browser, resolution, IP address, page URL, timestamp, operating system or other system related information for its analysis. 

**Inviting others to join Freeads.in**

By using Freeads.in you can also invite your friends by providing their email addresses, which will only be used to send invitation mail to the emails provided. 

**Contact Us**

For any further information or assistance in joining our platform, kindly write to us at [support@freeads.in](mailto:support@freeads.in)
